ebgames.ca 2019-04-28

# 

Last Updated: November 22, 2018

### EB Games' Commitment to Privacy

At EB Games Canada we are committed to your right to privacy. We collect personal information from our customers in the regular course of doing business. We have developed this Privacy Policy to explain our practices for the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information.

This Policy applies to our EB Games and GameStop retail stores (collectively, **"EB Games Stores"** ), our websites and to any other channels owned or operated by EB Games Canada that are used for the sale of products or services. All references to “websites” in this Privacy Policy mean [www.ebgames.ca](https://www.ebgames.ca/), www.gamestop.ca, or other EB Games Canada-provided websites (collectively, the **"EBG Websites"** ).

**IMPORTANT NOTICE:**

_**EB GAMES CANADA DOES NOT CARRY ON BUSINESS OR OTHERWISE HAVE OPERATIONS OR PREMISES OUTSIDE OF CANADA**_. THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT APPLY TO, NOR DOES EB GAMES CANADA HAVE ANY INVOLVEMENT WITH, THE STORES AND OPERATIONS OF ITS AFFILIATES, INCLUDING ANY EB GAMES STORES LOCATED OUTSIDE CANADA. THE EBG WEBSITES ARE INTENDED TO BE VIEWED BY INDIVIDUALS RESIDING IN CANADA. _**INDIVIDUALS RESIDING OUTSIDE OF CANADA ARE NOT AUTHORIZED TO ACCESS OR USE THE EBG WEBSITES**_. WITHOUT LIMITATION TO THE FOREGOING, INDIVIDUALS RESIDING OUTSIDE OF CANADA ARE NOT AUTHORIZED TO DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY PURCHASE GOODS OR SERVICES THROUGH ANY OF THE EBG WEBSITES OR PARTICIPATE IN ANY CONTEST OR OTHER PROMOTION OFFERED THROUGH ANY EBG WEBSITE. THE PRIVACY LAWS OF CANADA THEREFORE APPLY IN _EXCLUSIVITY_ TO PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED IN CONJUNCTION WITH YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF THE EBG WEBSITES. BY ACCESSING AN EBG WEBSITE, YOU HEREBY ACKNOWLEDGE AND CONFIRM YOUR UNDERSTANDING OF ALL OF THE FOREGOING FACTS. REFERENCES TO APPLICABLE LAWS REFER TO THE LAWS OF THE PROVINCE OF CANADA IN WHICH YOU RESIDE AND THE FEDERAL LAWS OF CANADA THAT APPLY IN SUCH PROVINCE. 

### How Do We Obtain Your Consent to the Collection of Your Personal Information?

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, place a pre-order, provide feedback, make an inquiry or return a purchase, we assume you consent to our collecting your personal information and using it for that specific purpose.

If we ask you for personal information for a secondary purpose, like contests, we will either ask you directly for your consent or provide you with an opportunity to say no. If you accept an offer made by any of our third party marketing partners, we will disclose your relevant personal information, including name, and address, to that third party, in accordance with the terms of the offer.

Express and Implied Consent – We may ask you to give your express consent, such as by checking a box to indicate your consent to receive marketing communications, or by providing your signature to indicate your acceptance of the use and disclosure terms presented on an application form. Other times, where permitted by applicable laws we may obtain your consent implicitly when we can reasonably conclude that you’ve given consent by some action you have taken or an action you have decided not to take. Generally, this occurs where the purpose for use of your personal information would be reasonably apparent to you or a natural extension of a purpose for which you have provided your express consent. For example, when you enter an EB Games Store, your attendance and activities in that EB Games Store may be recorded by our security cameras. By entering any EB Games Store you therefore implicitly consent to such recordings being created, used and retained for our internal security purposes and to investigate any security or unlawful incident that may occur at or near an EB Games Store, as well as to use in any civil or criminal proceedings to the extent the foregoing is relevant.

_How to Change or Withdraw Your Consent_ \- You may notify us at any time that you wish to withdraw or change your consent to our use and disclosure of your information. We will accommodate your request following receipt of such notice, subject to legal and contractual restrictions related to your transactions and the preservation of any rights and remedies that we may have as well as preservation of any evidence.

If you have "opted in" or subscribed to one of our newsletters or mailing lists, we will always provide you the opportunity to "opt out" or unsubscribe. For example, each e-newsletter we send to you will include a link or other method to unsubscribe or decline further e-newsletters.

When you choose to provide us with your personal information you consent to the use, disclosure and retention of your personal information as provided in this Privacy Policy and as may be further provided at or prior to the time of collection.

### What Information Do We Collect About You?

At EB Games Canada, we collect both personal information and non-personal information. The types of information we collect depend on the nature of your interaction with us. You may choose not to provide us with your personal information. However, if you make this choice we may not be able to provide you with the product, service, or information that you requested.

_Personal information_ \- Personal information is information that can identify an individual or information about an identifiable individual. We may collect personal information including the following:

  * contact information – your name, postal address, telephone number, and email address (or that of your parent or legal guardian if you are a minor)
  * validation information - your driver’s licence number or other government identification number (please note that we **_never_** collect your social insurance number or health card number)
  * personal preferences – opinions, interests, hobbies, product wish lists, language preferences, and marketing consent; and
  * financial information and transaction information – products purchased, method of payment, amount paid, credit or debit card number and other billing information.

_Non-personal information_ \- Non-personal information does not identify you as an individual. For example, we may collect certain non-personal data when you visit the EBG Websites, such as your Internet Protocol address, the type and version of browser you are using or the referring URL; or we may collect and summarize customer information in a non-personal, aggregate format for statistical and research purposes.

### How Do We Use Your Personal Information?

The primary reasons we collect personal information from you are:

  * to complete a sales transaction with you
  * to place pre-orders on your behalf
  * to fulfill your requests for products, services or information
  * to process trades
  * to process applications and other matters relating to Edge loyalty program memberships
  * to limit the possibility of fraud or error when we process your transactions, refunds and/or exchanges
  * to administer rebates
  * to conduct contests, promotions or surveys

We also use your personal information for other, secondary reasons, including:

  * Customer service
  * As part of extended service agreements
  * To administer a loyalty program, including but not limited to tracking and analyzing your purchases and preferences to better understand your product and service needs and eligibility
  * To facilitate your acceptance of offers made by our third party marketing partners
  * To tailor our online content based on your preferences
  * To measure and improve the effectiveness of the EBG Websites or our marketing endeavours
  * If you ask us, to offer and promote additional products and services we offer
  * For other purposes as described in this Privacy Policy
  * For other purposes disclosed to you at or prior to the time of collection
  * As otherwise provided or required by law

### Information EB Games Canada Collects Directly from You

_Returns and Exchanges_ – In connection with any returns, refunds or exchanges, we ask for personal information such as your name, address, email address and telephone number for the purposes of detecting and preventing fraud.

_Purchase Follow-Up and Surveys_ \- Following a purchase, we may send you a follow-up letter either thanking you for your business or inquiring as to whether you are satisfied with your purchase. We may use contact information collected from you to conduct occasional surveys and other customer research. These surveys are entirely voluntary.

_EB Games Stores_ – When you enter an EB Game Store your visit and activities in such EB Game Store will be recorded by our security cameras and retained and may be used for our internal security purposes as well as in conjunction with investigations, the preservation or enforcement of our rights and remedies, and/or any civil or criminal proceedings.

_EBG Websites_ – You can browse EBG Websites without having to provide us you’re your name. However, to order products and services from EBG Websites, or to use special features or functions of EBG Websites, you may be asked to provide personal information, such as your name, email address, postal address, telephone number, or credit or debit card information. We use this information to create your account, contact and correspond with you about your account or order, respond to your inquiries, and monitor functions or features of EBG Websites that you may use.

_Customer Reviews and Posted Content_ – We may provide you with the ability to rate or review products or services we sell, or otherwise post content on the EBG Websites. Any comments or reviews that you provide are accessible to all visitors to EBG Websites, so you should use discretion when posting information and you should not post personal information. EB Games Canada has no responsibility if you do post personal information on any EBG Website but will promptly remove such personal information if you make such request in writing. Subject to the other provisions of this privacy policy relating to your personal information, you grant a perpetual worldwide non-exclusive license to EB Games Canada to copy, use and/or display any content that you post on any EBG Website.

_Newsletters or Updates_ \- EB Games Canada may also offer you the opportunity to sign up for newsletters or other promotional communications. If you decide to do so, we will collect your contact information, such as name and email address. This information will only be used to send you the newsletter and promotional announcements that you have requested. You may “unsubscribe” at any time by using the unsubscribe link included in the footer of the newsletter or by using the unsubscribe link included below under the heading “Unsubscribe”. We do not rent our subscriber list or offer to sell it to other parties.

_Contest and Other Promotions_ \- From time to time, we may run contests or promotions. If you participate, you may be asked for contact information, confirmation that you have reached the age of majority in the province in which you reside and satisfy other eligibility requirements, as well as additional optional survey information (for example, product preferences). Personal information from contest entries will be used only to administer the contest and contact you if you win. For research and analysis purposes, we may also aggregate contest survey information in a manner that no longer identifies individual participants. All contests and promotions are subject to this Privacy Policy and the rules provided for each particular contest or promotion. If a contest is sponsored by a third party, it will be subject to the third party’s contest rules and policies.

_Subscription Services and Activations_ \- EB Games Canada may offer activation of certain products and services like online games, downloadable games or game components, or Internet services. These activations may require that certain contact and financial information be collected and provided to EB Games Canada or to its respective service providers as part of the activation process.

_Call Centres_ \- EB Games Canada operates customer support call centres to respond to your questions, concerns, or complaints regarding our products or services. When you contact our call centres, we may ask for personal information to help us respond to your inquiry or to verify your identity. For example, if you have a question about the status of a recent online order, we will ask for personal information to verify that you are the account holder. We may also monitor or record your telephone discussions with our customer support representatives for training purposes and to ensure service quality.

_EDGE Loyalty Program_ \- If you apply to register as a member to our EDGE loyalty program, you will be required to provide the following information: (i) first name; (ii) last name; (iii) date of birth; (iv) email address and type of e-mail account; (v) preferred language of communication; (vi) EB Games Store where application process is initiated; and (vii) phone number / mobile number. The following information may be provided at your discretion: (i) gender; (ii) profile photo; and (iii) postal code.

### Information EB Games Canada Collects Automatically

_EBG Websites_ \- When you visit the EBG websites, we may collect the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer and of your Internet service provider, the date and time you access the EBG Websites, the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to an EBG Website, the computer operating system you are using, the sections of the EBG Website you visit, the EBG Website pages read and images viewed, and the content you download from the website. This information is used for website and system administration purposes and to improve the EBG Websites.

_Cookies_ – EB Games Canada may use cookies to store your individual preferences and system information. “Cookies” are small electronic data files that websites can store on your computer for record keeping purposes. For example, cookies will remember what you've placed in your shopping cart, and tell us that you have visited one of the EBG Websites before. Cookies also may be used on the website for other reasons, such as to limit the number of times you have to enter a password or enter your language preference, to offer personalized web page content and information for your use, and to track your activity at the EBG Website. The use of cookies is standard in the Internet industry and many websites use them. In addition, you may modify your browser’s settings to notify you whenever a website is going to deposit a cookie on your computer’s hard drive or other storage media. The notification option generally gives you the opportunity to decide whether to accept or refuse a cookie in each instance. You can configure your browser to always disable cookies when cookies are being sent to your computer, although this may affect your ability to shop online, both at EB Games Canada and elsewhere.

_Website Tracking Information_ – Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. We may use web beacons (sometimes called “clear gifs”, “web bugs” or “pixel tags”) to compile tracking information reports regarding website user demographics, website traffic patterns, and website purchases. We may then provide these reports to advertisers and others. None of the tracking information in these reports can be connected to the identities or other personal information of individual users. In addition, we may use web beacons in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by the recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you do not want to receive these emails, please see the “unsubscribe” section below. For EB Games Canada’s own research purposes we may link tracking information with personal information voluntarily provided by website users. Once such a link is made, all of the linked information is treated as personal information and will be used and disclosed only in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

_Analytics Information_ \- We use the following third party tools and services to measure traffic to EBG Websites and how users interact with EBG Websites:

Alexa Metrics (<https://www.alexa.com/help/privacy>)

Google Analytics (<https://policies.google.com/privacy>)

Mouseflow (<https://mouseflow.com/privacy>)

Optimizely (<https://www.optimizely.com/privacy>)

New Relic (<https://newrelic.com/termsandconditions/privacy>)

Google Tag Manager (<https://policies.google.com/privacy>)

AddThis (<https://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy>)

Facebook Social Graph (<https://www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy>)

Google+ Platform (<https://policies.google.com/privacy>)

Pinterest (<https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy>)

Below is a list of data such third party services may collect in conjunction with your access and use of an EBG Website:

  * Account identifier (email)
  * Serving Domains
  * Referring/Exit pages/ URLs
  * URLs of web pages previously visited
  * Referring URLs to those web pages
  * IP addresses
  * Information about your system/device such as:
    * Device identifier(s)
    * web browser type and settings
    * Mobile network information including carrier name and phone number
    * browser engine
    * operating system
    * presence of use of apps
    * relevant version numbers
    * screen resolution
    * software installation and uninstall dates/time
  * First-party cookies
  * Google advertising cookies
  * Cookie IDs
  * Browsing history
  * Online user behaviour and Clickstream data such as:
    * Pages viewed
    * Page content selection
    * Clicks and touches
    * On-page time
    * Movements
    * Scrolls
    * Keystroke activities
  * Crash data
  * Other technical data
  * Date/Time
  * Demographic Data
  * Preferred language
  * Interaction Data
  * System activity
  * Ad Views
  * Internet Service Provider
  * Search History
  * Searches and search terms used
  * Key words selected or otherwise used
  * GPS location and other location Based Data
  * Preferred language
  * Purchases you make
  * The ads you see and how you use the third party advertiser’s services
  * Whether or not you have a Facebook account or are logged in to Facebook
  * Sensor data from your device
  * Information about things near your device, such as Wi-Fi access points, cell towers, and Bluetooth-enabled devices
  * Videos you watch
  * Voice and audio information when you use audio features
  * People with whom you communicate or share content
  * Activity on third-party sites and apps that use services of said service provider
  * Profile photo
  * Pinterest Pins
  * Your published comments and content

Please note that although these third party services collect information about you in conjunction with your visits and use of EBG Websites, EB Games Canada only receives _aggregated_ data from such service providers and we do not actually receive personal information about either you or any other user of any EBG Website. We would therefore invite you to access and review each such third party’s own privacy policy to determine how they collect, use, process, retain and communicate personal information. In some instances, it may be possible for you to configure your web browser to prevent the collection of some of the information that such third parties collect when you are visiting one of the EBG Websites.

_Social Media Platforms_ \- If you use embedded features on an EBG Website that posts content or otherwise links to your Facebook, Google, Twitter or other social media account, we will obtain general details about your social media account such as your user name and what content on the EBG Website you choose to share with other via one of your social media accounts.

_Links to Other Websites_ \- The EBG Websites may contain links that permit you to link to other websites or Internet resources. When you click on one of those links you are connecting to another website or Internet resource. EB Games Canada has no responsibility or liability for, or control over, those other websites or Internet resources or their collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of those other websites before you submit any personal information to them.

_Data on Returned Product_ – if you return products that may contain stored or recorded personal information, like computers, game consoles, etc., you are responsible for deleting or removing all personal information and media from your product before you return it. EB Games Canada is not responsible for any personal data or media that you do not delete or remove from such product.

_Supplementing Information_ \- From time to time we may supplement or editorialise information you give us with information from other sources, such as information validating your address or other available information you have provided to us. This is to help us maintain the accuracy of the information we collect and to help us provide better service.

### Does EB Games Canada Share Your Information?

EB Games Canada does not sell or rent our customers’ personal information to any other party. However, in the normal course of business we may share some of your personal information within our corporate family internationally and with third parties (such as agents, mandataries or service providers) acting on our behalf, or as permitted or required by law.

In addition, if you accept an offer from any of our third party marketing partners, we will share your contact with that specific third party, in accordance with the terms of the offer. If you have previously requested that your personal information not be shared with third party marketing partners, but then later consent by accepting a third party marketing offer available through one of the EBG Websites, we will share your contact and billing information with that specific third party, in accordance with the terms of the offer.

Some of these operations may result in personal information collected by EB Games Canada being stored or processed outside of Canada (including, the United States and the Republic of Ireland) and, as a result, your personal information may be accessible to law enforcement and regulatory authorities in accordance with the law of these foreign jurisdictions.

_Service Providers_ \- EB Games Canada may use third parties to manage one of more aspects of our business operations, including the processing or handling of personal information. We may share personal information with such third parties to perform services on our behalf such as fulfilling online orders, processing non-cash payments, sending marketing communications, servicing products, conducting research surveys, verifying and validating information that you have provided to us, delivering products, and providing customer support services. When we do use an outside service provider, we use contractual and other appropriate means to ensure that your personal information is used and safeguarded in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

EB Games Canada has taken precautions to prevent the fraudulent use of your information on the EBG Websites. EB Games Canada has adopted industry standard authentication procedures to ensure your protection while shopping with us online. This includes, but is not limited to, contacting financial institutions or credit reporting agencies to ensure the authenticity of your credit card and to validate your credit card billing information.

_Information Shared with Parent and Affiliates_ \- EB Games Canada may share personal information gathered on the EBG Websites within its organisation (including its retail stores) and with its corporate parent (domiciled in Luxembourg), and affiliates (including, affiliates domiciled in the United States and the Republic of Ireland ) for internal business purposes in accordance with this Privacy Policy . If EB Games Canada shares your information within its corporate family, we will ensure that your information continues to be used only in accordance with this Privacy Policy and your expressed choices.

_Product Safety Recalls_ \- In the event we receive notice from a manufacturer or supplier of a product safety recall, we may provide your contact information, limited to name, address and telephone number, to the manufacturer so that they may notify you of the recall and supply details of any replacement or repair programs. This transfer of your contact information will occur only for recalls that may impact your personal safety or impair the functionality of the product you purchased from us.

_Sale or Transfer of Business or Assets of EB Games Canada_ \- Any information we have about you may be transferred or disclosed to a purchaser or prospective purchaser in the event of a sale, assignment, or other transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets either directly or indirectly (including one affecting or relating to EB Games Canada’ parent). Should such a sale, assignment or other transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure that the transferee uses your information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

_Legal Disclosure_ \- EB Games Canada may disclose your information as permitted or required by law. For example, we may be compelled to release information by a court of law or other person or entity with jurisdiction to compel production of such information. If we have reasonable grounds to believe information could be useful in the investigation of improper or unlawful activity, we may disclose information to law enforcement agencies or other appropriate investigative bodies.

### How does EB Games Canada Protect Your Information?

The file containing your personal information will be stored on our servers and will only be accessible to our employees and those of our agents, mandataries and service providers who require it in the course of their duties. EB Games Canada takes appropriate steps to protect your personal information. We maintain appropriate safeguards and current security standards to protect your personal information against unauthorized access, disclosure, or misuse. For example, electronic records are stored in secure, limited-access servers; electronic data is stored behind secured encryption access; we use technological tools like firewalls and passwords; and we ensure our employees are trained on the importance of maintaining the security and confidentiality of personal information.

_SSL Technology_ \- EBG Websites use encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”), to protect your personal information during data transport. SSL encrypts ordering information such as your name, address, and credit card number.

_VeriSign Certification_ \- EBG Websites have received a VeriSign certificate to confirm that we have met with industry standard security protocols. For your online security, always verify you are on an authentic EB Games Canada website by clicking on the VeriSign logo located in the lower right footer of our homepage. Make sure that the URL of the VeriSign confirmation page begins with "[https://seal.verisign.com](https://seal.verisign.com/)".

_Choosing a Password_ \- When you create an online account on EBG Websites, you will be prompted to select a personal password. To maximize your level of protection, you should choose a strong personal password, which means that you should use at least 6 characters including a combination of both letters and numbers. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and any account information. EB Games Canada will never send an unsolicited communication asking you for your password or requesting that you update and disclose your account credentials or any billing or payment information. WE WILL NEVER REQUEST THAT YOU DISCLOSE YOUR SOCIAL INSURANCE NUMBER, HEALTH INSURANCE NUMBER, PASSWORDS OR ANY OTHER SENSITIVE INFORMATION ONLINE OR BY E-MAIL. BE CAREFUL WHEN CLICKING ON ANY HYPERLINKS EMBEDDED IN ANY E-MAIL ADVISING YOU OF ANY SUSPENSION OF ACCOUNT, TRANSACTION CONFIRMATION OR THE LIKE AND ALWAYS CAREFULLY LOOK AT THE URL OF THE SITE YOU ARE REDIRECTED TO AND ENSURE THAT YOU ARE IN FACT ON A EBG WEBSITE AND NOT AN ILLEGITIMATE IMITATION THEREOF. Although we cannot take responsibility for any theft, misuse, unauthorized disclosure, loss, alteration or destruction of data by a third party, we take reasonable precautions to prevent such occurrences.

### How Can You Verify Your Information?

You may check your information to verify, update, or correct it, and to have any obsolete information removed. If you created an account on one of the EBG Websites, you can access and change your online account profile yourself. You can also ask to review any of the information that we have retained, how we have used it, and to whom we have disclosed it at any time by contacting us as indicated below under the heading “Contacting EB Games Canada”. Subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law, and provided we can authenticate your identity, you will be given reasonable access to your personal information, and will be entitled to challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and to have it amended as appropriate. You may also ask us to change your preferences regarding how we use or disclose your information, or let us know that you do not wish to receive any further communication from us. Again, the withdrawal of your consent or your request limiting our ability to use, retain or communicate your personal information may prevent the delivery of products to you or your access to and/or use of the EBG Websites.

### When is Your Information Removed?

We keep your information only as long as we need it for legitimate business purposes and to meet any legal requirements. We have retention standards that meet these parameters. We securely destroy your information when it is no longer needed, or we remove your personally identifiable information to render it anonymous.

### Contacting EB Games Canada

EB Games Canada is responsible for all personal information under its control. Our Privacy Compliance Manager is accountable for EB Games Canada's compliance with the principles described here. If you have any questions, concerns or complaints about the privacy practices of our organization please contact us at the following:

Email: [Click here](https://www.ebgames.ca/Help/Index?section=Privacy#Reminder) (please read the Important Reminder below)

You may contact our Privacy Compliance Manager by email at [privacy@ebgames.ca](mailto:privacy@ebgames.ca) or by mail at:

> Privacy Compliance EB Games   
>  Electronics Boutique Canada Inc.   
>  8995 Airport Road   
>  Brampton, Ontario   
>  L6T 5T2 

We will promptly respond to your request or investigate your concern but no later than 30 days from the date of receipt of your query and validation of your identity in terms of any inquiry or request relating to your personal information.

_Important Reminder about email communications:_ Please remember that an email sent over the Internet is not secure. If you send an email directly to us from your own email account the content thereof will not be encrypted. We strongly recommend that you do not send sensitive information (like a credit card number) to us via unencrypted email. EB Games Canada is not responsible for any transmission by you of any personal information over the Internet.

### Unsubscribe

If you no longer wish to be contacted regarding promotions, new product and entertainment releases [click here](https://www.ebgames.ca/Account/LogOn?ReturnUrl=%2fMyAccount%2fCommunications).

### Who is EB Games Canada?

The EBG Websites and EB Games Stores are owned and operated by Electronics Boutique Canada Inc. (cob EB Games).

### Will this Privacy Policy change?

To accommodate changes in our services, changes in technology, and legal developments, this Privacy Policy may change over time without notice to you. We may add, change, or remove portions of the Privacy Policy when we feel it is appropriate to do so. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy periodically and, more specifically, the date of last revision set forth at the very beginning of this Privacy Policy. Each time you submit personal information or use our services you agree to be bound by the then current terms of the Privacy Policy. Whenever we update the Privacy Policy we will change the date to indicate when the changes were made. Personal information previously provided will be subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of collection or at the time of consent (as the case may be).

### Change History:

_October 19, 2009:_ Format, structure and general revisions to improve readability and user-friendliness of content, and to add additional detailed information regarding collection and use of personal information.

_November 22, 2018:_ Revisions to improve readability and user-friendliness of content and to reflect changes in terms of data management practices and inter-company exchanges of personal information.
